kogama.com 2019-12-26

# Privacy Policy - KoGaMa - Play, Create And Share Multiplayer Games

Updated: July 10, 2019

## 1\. General

This Privacy Policy governs the collection of personally identifiable information on all platforms on which KoGaMa ("The Service") provides its services, i.e. the kogama.com and kogama.com.br websites, any website(s) on which our games are embedded, or in connection with the use of The Service's mobile apps available on Google Play and the Apple App Store.

We aim to collect only the minimum necessary data to operate the site, and likewise to keep data storage duration to a minimum. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of the terms and conditions of The Service. Please refer to the Data Collection section below for information on what personal data we process, and how we store this data.

By registering for an account, accessing or using The Service, users agree to be bound by the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

  * We store your IP adress in order to facilitate technical operation of the site, as well as to be facilitate safety for our users
  * We store your email address if you provide us with it and you are old enough to do so.
  * We use ads to keep the service operational. If you’re under 13, we do not share any personal data as a result of this, but otherwise you give us consent to share certain data with our partners to facilitate a personalized ad service (See below for more).

### 1.2 Cookies

The Service uses cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data (a small file) sent to your computer or device by a website. In general, when you visit The Service, cookies will be placed on your device that help us provide you with a good browsing experience and also allow us to improve its website and display adds. More specifically, The Service uses cookies for the following purposes:

  * Web Analytics. We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google. Google Analytics places cookies on your device to help distinguish between different visitors and to analyze how users use The Service. The cookies placed by Google on your device are used to collect certain information, such as the date and time that a user visits us, the number of times a user has visited us and The Service that has directed the user to us. More information on the use of cookies by Google Analytics can be found on Google’s website.
  * Functional Cookies. We also place cookies on your device to make navigating The Service easier. These cookies are used to allow the website to remember choices you made and provide for enhanced, more personal features. For instance, these cookies can be used to remember the status of your login, or to allow you to return to a previous page.
  * Social Media. Social media can place cookies through The Service to integrate social media (i.e. LinkedIn, Twitter, Google+ and Facebook). You agree to place these cookies on your device by clicking on the social media buttons to activate them. These social media have their own privacy and cookie policies, which we do not control. Please check the social media websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.
  * Ads. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this and other websites. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to the users of The Service based on their visit to The Service and/or other sites on the Internet. You can visit aboutads.info to opt out of third party interest based ad cookies.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. Please note that if you do so, The Service will not function as intended.

## 2\. Purchases

All product purchases are processed by one of our platform specific payment service providers: PaymentWall, Google Pay or Apple Pay. Please refer to their privacy policies for additional information.

### 2.1 Desktop & Web

### 2.2 Android

### 2.3 iOS

## 3\. Data collection

We receive and store certain types of information whenever users visit the site. In addition to the information individuals provide explicitly on The Service (An anonymous username, voluntary e-mail address ), we may collect the name of the domain and host from which users access the Internet; the IP address of the computer used; the browser and operating system used; the date and time of access; and the Internet address from which you arrived at The Service (including any search terms used to find The Service through a search engine such as Google).

### 3.1 Your KoGaMa account

To use all functionalities on The Service you must create a KoGaMa account. Upon creation of a KoGaMa account, we ask you to choose a username - please be sure to pick one that doesn’t include any personally identifiable information. We also ask you to identify your month and year of birth in order to identify extra needs for consent. You will also be asked to provide an e-mail address if you’re above the age of consent. This is entirely voluntary, and if you choose to do so it will only be used to communicate news from the games on The Service.

You may play games on The Service without creating an account.

### 3.2 User-to-user communication

The Service allows users to communicate in a number of ways. Private chat and in-game messages are only stored long enough to ensure stable delivery and then deleted. Note: revealing personally identifiable information is against the Terms and conditions, and it should not occur. Any personally identifiable information revealed in online activities will be available to others who can access this content. We will delete personally identifiable information, if we are made aware of a breach of this rule.

### 3.3 GDPR consent

Upon accessing The Service, you will be presented with a dialogue that allows you to either consent to us processing personal data as outlined in this Privacy Policy, or to decline to the processing of personal data. If you consent, you may choose to withdraw your consent at any time by accessing the menu at the top right and selecting, "Remove consent".

If you withdraw your consent, we will cease processing of the data for which you have withdrawn consent, unless we have a legal obligation to keep some or parts of your data. The withdrawal of your consent does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on your consent before its withdrawal.

## 4\. Data Security

We utilize physical, administrative and technical safeguards to ensure the security and integrity of our systems used to store personally identifiable information. We use server hosting provided by ISO 27001 certified providers to comply with International Organization for Standardizations standard for data protection. We cannot, however, guarantee the security of any information transmitted to The Service. Nor can we guarantee that any such information is not being accessed, altered or destroyed by a breach, circumvention, failure or interruption of security measures. Users can always request access to a copy of any stored data, provided they can be clearly identified in relation to the data.

### 4.1 Disclosing personally identifiable information

We aim to delete any info that has been given to us in violation of the terms and conditions; however, we may disclose information to third parties in the following circumstances:

We may disclose information to others who provide services to us in order to operate, maintain and enhance the features of The Service, such as website hosting services providers. The use of personally identifiable information is limited to the use needed in order to furnish those services to us. These providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

### 4.2 Legal obligations

We may disclose information to others if we believe in good faith that the disclosure is necessary to comply with the requirements of applicable laws, to respond to court orders, judicial or regulatory subpoenas and information requests or to otherwise comply with law enforcement. We may disclose information to others if we believe such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to take precautions against liability or to enforce our rights; to protect us and users from unlawful or abusive activity; to investigate and defend ourselves against claims or allegations from third parties; to protect the security or integrity of The Service; or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of The Service, our users or third parties.

### 4.3 Voluntary disclosure

Users may choose to disclose personally identifiable information in various interactive areas of The Service. These include, but are not limited to the user's public profile page, the in-game chat, or as part of user-created games. Disclosing personally identifiable information in this way is not encouraged. Once personally identifiable information is made available, it can be collected and used by any person who has access to this content without restriction.

If you have accidentally disclosed personal information, please contact our support.

## 5\. Advertisements

The Service displays advertisements to all non-subscribing users. The way this happens depends on the platform on which The Service is accessed.

### 5.1 Mobile advertisements

Accessing The Service from a mobile device will expose the device's advertising ID and IP address. We use the ad mediation servicea provided by Fyber. Fyber's privacy policy is available here:

You can configure privacy settings on your phone to block this.

### 5.2 Desktop advertisements

Accessing The Service from a desktop device will activate Google’s ad cookies. You can read more here (including about opting out):

## 6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

The provisions of this Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time without notice and at Multiverse ApS’ sole discretion. We will post any revised Privacy Policy on this page and show the date the revised Privacy Policy was modified and the effective date of the modifications. If we make material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Continued access or use of The Service constitutes acceptance of any modifications of the Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about your data, please feel free to reach out to our support.
